Guide to the Wilmarth Sheldon Lewis Papers
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Correspondence, 1901–1979; Series I; 76.56; 181 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Westergaard, Waldemar, 1882-1963, 1944–1962 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Western Hemisphere Inc., 1976–1977 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Weston, John C. (John Charles), 1963–1964 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Wetherbee, Raymond and Helen, 1942–1952 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Wetmore, Edith Malvina Keteltas, 1870-1966, 1938–1940 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Wheaton College (Norton, Mass.), 1975 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Wheeler-Bennett, John Wheeler, Sir, 1902-1975, 1971–1975 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Whipple, Jay N., 1971 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Whitaker, Jeremy, 1971 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - White, Terence De Vere, 1955–1963 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - White, Wade, 1909-1995, 1936–1957 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Whitehead, Helen Cowles, 1936 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Whitehead, John S., 1976–1977 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Whitehill, Walter Muir, 1905-1978, 1953–1975 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Whitehouse, Mary Crocker Alexander, 1895-1986, 1960–1973 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Whitney, John Hay and Betsey, 1950–1971 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Whitridge, Arnold, 1891-1989, and Janetta, 1933–1973 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Widener, Joseph E. (Joseph Early), 1872-1943, 1938 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Wickwire, Franklin B., 1958–1966 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Wiggin, Frederick H., 1950–1961 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Wiggin, Lewis M., 1950–1955 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Wight, Charles A., 1936–1945 (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - Wight, Eliot, 1940–1948 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Wilcox, Austin K., 1974 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Wilcox, Vincent, 1966–1968 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Wilder, Amos N. (Amos Niven), 1895-1993, 1914, 1957-1979 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      Also present is one letter (1914) from Lewis to Wilder, written on Wilder's bronco stationery.
    - Wilder, Fessenden, 1961–1972 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Wilder, Isabel, 1900-1995, 1947–1979 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975, and Dixie, 1943–1975 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Wilkins, Paul L., 1979 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - William H. Robinson, Ltd., 1933–1956 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Wm. Dawson & Sons, 1958–1974 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - William Salt Library, 1950–1954 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Frank O. H., 1955–1967 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Harold Herbert, Sir, 1880-1964, 1939–1957 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Iolo Aneurin, 1890-1962, 1934–1936 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Williams, Ralph M., 1938–1964 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Stanley Thomas, 1888-1956, 1933–1955 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Wayland Wells, 1888-1945, 1925–1953 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Williamson, George Charles, 1858-1942, 1938–1939 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Williamson, Reginald Ross, 1951–1962 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Wilmerding, John, 1975–1979 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Barbara K., 1971–1974 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Richard R., 1971–1979 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Wimsatt, William K. (William Kurtz), 1907-1975, 1951–1973 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Winckworth, Chauncey, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Wing, H. J. R., 1959–1967 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Wing, Donald Goddard, 1904-1972, 1936–1962 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Winifred A. Myers, Ltd., 1958–1978 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Winn, Charles J. F., 1948–1952 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Winship, George Parker, 1871-1952, 1936–1944 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Winslow, F. E., 1955–1967 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Winter, William L., 1955–1956 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Wolf, Edwin, 1911-1991, 1955–1978 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Wolfers, Arnold, 1892-1968, 1939–1955 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Wood, George Robert, 1937–1938 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Wood, William P. and Mia, 1967–1976 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Woodbridge, Henry S., 1977–1979 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Woods, William, 1948–1949 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Woof, R. S., 1961–1965 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Woollen, Evans, 1927-, 1936–1947 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Woolley, Monty, 1888-1963, 1943–1954 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Woolley, John E., 1943–1963 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Woolsey, John Munro, 1877-1945, 1940–1942 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Worcester College (University of Oxford), 1947 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - William P. Wreden Books & Manuscripts (Firm), 1947–1976 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Wright, Austin, 1904-1979, 1936–1949 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Wright, James, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Wyckoff, James, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Wyman, Willard G. (Willard Gordon), 1898-1969, 1975–1978 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Wynne, Marjorie G., 1949–1978 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - X, general (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Ximenes: Rare Books, 1966–1976 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Ya-Yz, general (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - Yale Alumni Association of Cleveland, 1938–1941 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Yale Bibliophiles, 1974–1977 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Yale Clubs, 1949–1979 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Yale Co-op, 1971–1975 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Yale Editions of the Private Papers of James Boswell, 1950–1962 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Yale Review, 1946–1969 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Yale University. Jared Eliot Association., 1933–1960 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Yale University Press, 1920–1959 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Yale University Press, 1933–1960 (Box 151, Folder 9-11)
      Correspondence in these four folders, and those in Box 152, primarily concerns publication of the Yale Edition of Horace Walpole's Correspondence.
    - Yale University Press, 1961–1979 (Box 152, Folder 1-4)
    - Yale University Printing Service, 1973–1974 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Yale University. Torch Honor Society., 1945–1950 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Yeamans Hall Club, 1952–1967 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - York Minster. Library, 1958–1973 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Young, Frances, 1946–1959 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Young, George Berkeley, 1913-, 1944–1970 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Young, Karl, 1879-1943, 1931–1949 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Young, Mary, 1975 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Yvon, Paul, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Z, general (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Zapffe, Carl Andrew, 1977 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Zeitlin & Ver Brugge (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1951–1976 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Zimmerman, William, 1890-1967, 1946–1957 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - "Nuisance", 1945–1974 (Box 153, Folder 11)
      "Nuisance" holds letters Lewis received from people he considered to be just that. Accordingly, he marked some of their letters so and filed them in an eponymous folder. They are predominantly from writers who had read about Lewis in a magazine or had encountered one of his publications and were sending questions he generally felt didn't need to answer. Some contain a plea for money or help with Walpole genealogy (queries such as "I am in search of the ancestors of Caesar Walpole, my direct ancestor."). Several writers sought appraisals of old books, or offered for sale materials, both old and new; a man from Minneapolis asked in 1950 if Lewis would like to buy his recently acquired set of the Yale Edition of Walpole-Mann correspondence.
    - Unidentified correspondents, 1930–1979 (Box 153, Folder 12-13)
  - Chapman-Lewis-Whibley Correspondence
    The subseries holds letters sent among three scholarly colleagues and friends, Wilmarth Lewis, R. W. Chapman (1881-1960), and Leonard Whibley (1862-1941). The Chapman-Lewis correspondence, amounting to more than 1,800 letters, forms the bulk of the material, and documents the close relationship that the men maintained for thirty years. They exchanged letters regularly, often several times a week, from 1929 through shortly before Chapman's death in 1960, and it was Chapman's wish that their letters be kept together in Lewis's library. In a 1944 note to his wife Katherine, Chapman wrote: "When I am gone I think Lefty might like to have his letters to me (which no one else could ever decipher); he has kept all of mine. Also the Chapman-Whibley correspondence. RWC 6.10.44." Katherine Chapman transferred the letters, including those between her husband and the Cambridge scholar Whibley, to Wilmarth Lewis in 1966.
    R. W. Chapman was only half-correct in his legibility assessment: he also had handwriting quite difficult to decipher and the two often wrote almost in code, with some sentences just phrases with acronyms. In 1979 an effort was made by the library staff to transcribe (to the best of the typist's ability) the manuscript correspondence but the project faltered after the 1942 letters were completed. Chapman's letters are particularly vexing due to their calligraphy and complexity: during and after the war he wrote mostly on the verso of any available paper he could obtain, such as printers' proof sheets, galleys, ephemera, press announcements, and even incoming office correspondence. For instance, Chapman's October 10, 1946, letter was written on the verso of pages from an edited manuscript on Greek philosophy, and his January 20, 1952, letter appeared on the back of one to him from the calligrapher Aubrey West. In addition, many of Chapman's letters were composed over several days (they are dated internally throughout the narrative) and run to several pages, which he consecutively numbered in the upper right corner of each leaf. However, because he wrote on combinations of disparate papers—some literally scraps—and his writing is so difficult to read, many orphan leaves appear at the end of each year's folder.
    Over the years, the content of their correspondence changed from scholarly research inquiries to a mix of personal and professional topics, always with the latest news of friends and colleagues—including those at Yale—and the Chapman's three sons and their families. Horace Walpole, books, Jane Austen, bibliography, and Lewis's acquisitions are the most consistent primary subjects, but an omnipresent theme was World War II. It was discussed with anticipation in many letters written between 1936 and 1940, and once the war started, the hardships began. Of the few (less than thirty) letters in the collection from Katherine Chapman, most focus on the family's gratitude for the packages of food, particularly the Virginia hams, that the Lewises had sent to them from various purveyors, as well as her requests for raisins, nuts (but not peanuts or coconut), and most especially sugar, butter, lemon juice, and dried onion flakes. The shipments continued after the war ended; one letter, dated January 28, 1953, was two typed pages only describing the fate of the Irish ham sent by the Lewises for Christmas.
    Also in the correspondence are many third-party letters sent as enclosures from Chapman to Lewis, such as one of May 10, 1950, from author Elizabeth Jenkins (1905-2010), which describes her visit to Matson House in Gloucestershire and in which she drew a sketch of the windows that Horace Walpole had installed there. However, most of the letters are from scholars and librarians, and concern/confirm fine points related to bibliography and Walpole, or any of the many topics that the two men covered in their letters to each other.
    Their mutual friend Leonard Whibley, a lecturer and fellow at his alma mater, Pembroke College, University of Cambridge, was co-editor of the Correspondence of Thomas Gray (Oxford: Clarendon Press, 1935) and, like Chapman, an early member of the Walpole Correspondence Advisory Board. In their letters to each other, Chapman and Lewis wrote often of their friend, for whom they used an affectionate nickname, "D.M." (short for "Doddy Man") and his wife, the noted suffragette Henrietta Barwell (1878-1949) known as "Rhita." The Lewises would regularly visit both men's homes on their trips to England, and after Whibley died in November 1941, Lewis wrote to Chapman that he was the first member of the Walpole Edition advisory board that had ever been dropped from the Walpole edition's masthead. Chapman retrieved Lewis's letters to Whibley from Rhita Whibley and they were returned to Lewis. Thus, filed in this subseries are the letters sent between Lewis and Chapman, Chapman and Whibley, and Lewis and Whibley.
    - Chapman, R. W. (Robert William) and Katherine Metcalfe Chapman
      - Census of Chapman-Lewis correspondence, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
        Compiled by Lewis and library staff.
      - Letters between Chapman and Lewis, 1926–1936 (Box 154, Folder 2-10)
      - Letters between Chapman and Lewis, 1937–1941 (Box 155, Folder 1-7)
      - Letters between Chapman and Lewis, 1941–1947 (Box 156, Folder 1-8)
      - Letters between Chapman and Lewis, 1948–1952 (Box 157, Folder 1-7)
      - Letters between Chapman and Lewis, 1952–1966 (Box 158, Folder 1-5)
      - Unidentified notes and clippings, 1947, 1966, unidentified (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - Published writings by Chapman, 1937–1944 (Box 336 (Oversize), Folder 3)
        Tear sheets from The Times Literary Supplement including Chapman's review "The Walpole Correspondence: Portrait of an Age" (July 24, 1937).
      - Photographs of R. W. Chapman, 1939–1949 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - "Strawberry Hill in New England", 1952 July 24 (Box 333 (Oversize), Folder 1)
        Tear sheet from the BBC's weekly magazine The Listener, featuring a transcript of Chapman's review of Collector's Progress.
      - Chapman telephone directory, undated (Box 333 (Oversize), Folder 2)
        Manuscript list of local purveyors and friends, with their telephone numbers, found among the 1953 letters.
      - "Latin without Tears", undated (Box 158, Folder 8)
        Autograph manuscript in parts, written on the versos of other authors' typescript manuscripts. Sent to Lewis in 1948.
      - Chapman, Robin and William, 1955–1966 (Box 158, Folder 9)
        Correspondence with the sons of R. W. Chapman
    - Whibley, Leonard and Rhita Barwell
      - Letters between Chapman and Whibley, 1925–1941 (Box 159, Folder 1)
      - Letters between Lewis and the Whibleys, 1931–1949 (Box 159, Folder 2-10)
      - Notes and letter to D. Massey, 1939, undated (Box 159, Folder 11)
      - Lewis correspondence count, undated (Box 159, Folder 12)
      - Photographs of Whibley and The Dial House, 1933, undated (Box 159, Folder 13)
      - Envelope formerly holding letters returned by Chapman, 1942 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Lewis Family Correspondence
    The subseries contains only correspondence with Wilmarth Lewis's family members; correspondence with relatives of Annie Lewis in the Auchincloss, Jennings, and other families are filed in the first subseries, General Correspondence. Correspondence between Wilmarth and Annie Lewis is filed in the Annie Burr Lewis Papers (LWL MSS 21), Box 2, folders 10-15.
    Arranged alphabetically by family member.
    - Danforth, Joan Lewis, 1940–1979 (Box 160, Folder 1-3)
      The niece of Wilmarth Lewis, Joan Maitland Lewis was the daughter Martha Mohun Maitland and her first husband; she was adopted by Azro Lewis Jr. after his marriage to Martha in 1937. Joan attended Mills College, graduated from Stanford University in 1953, and lived first in San Francisco and then in New York. She became the second wife of Robert Scofield Danforth (1926-1987) in 1974, and was a business partner with Wilmarth Lewis in inherited ranchland in California.
      The correspondence here covers both personal and business affairs, as Joan reported news of her parents, her uncle Charles Lewis, and her own life and travels to her uncle Wilmarth, in addition to serving as the business and contracts manager for the ranch properties they owned jointly in California (which Joan often referred to as "our farming venture"). The actual business correspondence sent between the partners and their financial and legal advisors, as well as contracts, leases, and other documents, can be found in Series VII, Real Estate Records, Boxes 288-289.
    - Lewis, Azro Nathaniel, 1908 November 8 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      Contains a single letter from Wilmarth Lewis to his father, with a request for an allowance.
    - Lewis, Azro Nathaniel, Jr., 1918–1944 (Box 160, Folder 5-6)
      Azro Nathaniel Lewis Jr. (1883-1957) was the third of Azro Lewis's five sons, and the first born to him and his second wife Miranda Sheldon Lewis. He graduated from Stanford University in 1906 and married Martha Mohun Maitland in 1937.
      Includes a letter from Lewis to Mrs. Cowles, discussing Wilmarth Lewis's purchase of the Cowles house.
    - Lewis, Azro Nathaniel, Jr., 1945–1956 (Box 161, Folder 1-3)
    - Lewis, Charles Lux and Minna Conger
      Charles Lux Lewis (1885-1969) was the fourth of Azro N. Lewis's five sons, and the second son born to him and his second wife Miranda Sheldon Lewis. Charles attended Stanford University but did not graduate. He married Minna Ethelind Conger in 1910 and settled in San Francisco; the couple had no children. Charles Lewis became the family's representative on the board of the Miranda Lux Foundation, created in 1953 after the close of Lux College, founded by his great-aunt Miranda Lux.
      - Correspondence, 1893, 1922-1969 (Box 161, Folder 4-6)
        The earliest item (1893) is a letter from Charles to his brother George, sent to Wilmarth Lewis on June 18, 1965.
      - Correspondence, 1968–1969 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Notes and correspondence related to Charles's health, 1968–1969 (Box 162, Folder 2)
        Wilmarth Lewis's correspondence with Charles's doctor, financial advisor, and friend regarding his health and situation, as well as notes on telephone conversations.
      - Obituaries and tributes for Charles and Minna, 1969–1970 (Box 162, Folder 3-4)
      - Charles Lewis diaries, 1901, 1908 (Box 162, Folder 5)
        Sent to Wilmarth Lewis in June 1965 with other family history material.
      - Conger family documents, 1847–1910 (Box 162, Folder 6)
        Includes two marriage certificates from the wedding of Nelson P. Conger and Eliza L. Crane (1847, Paw Paw, Michigan); an invitation to the wedding of their daughter Harriet Conger to Sidney J. Conger (1883, Paw Paw); an invitation to the wedding their daughter Minna to Charles Lewis (1910, Alameda, California); and a photograph of Harriet Conger (1899).
    - Lewis, George Welcome, 1885, 1923-1947 (Box 162, Folder 7)
      George Welcome Lewis (1871-1951) was the second eldest of Wilmarth Lewis's two half-brothers. The son of Azro Lewis and his first wife Marie Stillman Lewis, George graduated from Amherst College in 1893, and settled in California. His Lewis family genealogical work began in 1894 and was continued after his death by his half-brother Charles. George and his wife Edythe (1881-1949) had no children.
      Includes one letter (1885) to George Lewis from his maternal grandmother Harriet Wells Stillman (1819-1900), and one (1923) from George Lewis to Charles Lewis.
    - Lewis, George and Betty, 1939–1979 (Box 162, Folder 8-9)
      George Lewis (1927- ) was the son of Ralph and Ruth Lewis; with his first wife Betty (-1972) he had two children, John and Joanne.
      Includes letters from George's wives Betty and Donna, and son John.
    - Lewis, Martha Mohun, 1956–1979 (Box 162, Folder 10)
      Martha Mohun Maitland Lewis (1900-1983) was the wife of Azro N. Lewis Jr. She and her daughter Joan maintained a close relationship with Wilmarth Lewis after the death of Azro in 1957, arranging visits in California and Connecticut, and exchanging holiday gifts.
    - Lewis, Miranda Wilmarth Sheldon
      Miranda Sheldon Lewis (1860-1922) was the second wife of Azro N. Lewis, and the mother of Azro, Charles, and Wilmarth Lewis.
      The letters were written between Wilmarth Lewis and his mother in the years surrounding Lewis's military service in England and France as a member of the American Expeditionary Forces during World War I. They, and other early family letters, were transcribed by Ruth Day in the summer of 1980.
      - Letters to and from Charles Lewis, 1913–1922 (Box 163, Folder 1)
        The earliest is a photographic postcard of George.
      - Letters to Wilmarth Lewis, 1915-1920, undated (Box 163, Folder 2-3)
      - Letters from Wilmarth Lewis, 1917–1919 (Box 163, Folder 4-7)
    - Lewis, Ruth Stokes Morris, 1940–1963 (Box 163, Folder 8)
      Ruth Lewis (1896-1964) was the wife of Ralph S. Lewis (1875-1946), Wilmarth Lewis's second oldest half-brother.
    - Mainwaring, Joanne Lewis, 1953–1975 (Box 163, Folder 9)
      Joanne Mainwaring (1930-2004) was the daughter of Ralph S. Lewis and his wife Ruth.
  - Responses to Publications
    Lewis kept folders of letters and notes he received responding to publications written or published by him, and those written about him; they include personal letters from friends and family, as well as acknowledgements from institutions. Most of the writers in this subseries also have folders of correspondence in Series I.
    - "The Accords and Resemblances of Johnson and Walpole", 1967–1968 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      Paper given at a meeting of The Johnsonians, September 16, 1967, and published afterward
    - Atlantic Monthly articles, 1945–1948 (Box 164, Folder 2)
      "The Bookseller as Teacher" (February 1947)
    - A Catalogue of Horace Walpole's Library (New Haven: Yale University Press, 1969), 1969–1970 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Collector's Progress (New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1951), 1951–1952 (Box 164, Folder 4-6)
      Includes a letter from President Harry S. Truman.
    - "Genesis of Strawberry Hill", 1934 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - "Horace Walpole" Mellon lectures, 1958–1960 (Box 164, Folder 8)
      Comments on presentations of the A. W. Mellon Lectures in the Fine Arts (delivered at the National Gallery, Washington, 1960), made in try-outs in New Haven (1958-1959) and broadcast on the radio from Washington (1960).
    - Horace Walpole (New York: Pantheon Books, 1960), 1960–1961 (Box 164, Folder 9)
      The American publication of the A. W. Mellon Lectures in the Fine Arts delivered at the National Gallery.
    - Horace Walpole (London: Rupert Hart-Davis, 1961) (Box 164, Folder 10)
      The British publication of the A. W. Mellon Lectures in the Fine Arts delivered at the National Gallery.
    - Horace Walpole, Writer, Politician, and Connoisseur (New Haven: Yale University Press, 1967), 1966–1968 (Box 165, Folder 1)
      Festschrift for Wilmarth Sheldon Lewis; essays on the 250th anniversary of Walpole's birth, edited by Warren Hunting Smith.
    - Horace Walpole's Library (Cambridge [Eng.]: At the University Press, 1958), 1957–1958 (Box 165, Folder 2-3)
      The Sandars Lectures delivered at Cambridge. May 7-9, 1957.
    - "Miscellaneous Antiquities" series
      "Miscellaneous Antiquities" was a series of fourteen small publications written or edited by Lewis between 1927 and 1940, in the spirit of (and meant to continue) the two "Miscellaneous Antiquities" issued by Horace Walpole at Strawberry Hill in 1772; in Lewis's case, they were produced and sent as a year-end gift to friends, family, colleagues, and libraries. While most were privately printed and distributed for Lewis by Edmund B. Thompson, at his Hawthorn House press in Windham, Connecticut, a few were published in conjunction with the Grolier Club, Oxford University Press, and Yale University Press.
      - 6. The Forlorn Printer: Being Notes on Horace Walpole's Alleged Neglect of Thomas Kirgate, 1931–1932 (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - 7. Anecdotes Told Me by Lady Denbigh, 1932–1933 (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - 8. Horace Walpole's Letters from Madame de Sévigné, 1933–1934 (Box 165, Folder 6)
      - 9. Some Short Observations for the Lady Mary Stanhope Concerning the Writing of Ordinary Letters, by Philiip, Second Earl of Chesterfield., 1934–1935 (Box 165, Folder 7)
      - 10. Le Triomphe de l'Amitié, ou, l'Histoire de Jacqueline et de Jeanneton, 1935–1936 (Box 165, Folder 8)